question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Politics",
      "question": "The S in Harry S. Truman stands for &quot;Samuel&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the "
                  "Revolutionary War.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Bill Cipher in the show &quot;Gravity Falls&quot; is the good guy.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Science: Computers",
      "question": "The Python programming language gets its name from the British comedy group &quot;Monty "
                  "Python.&quot;",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot; and &quot;The Legend of Korra&quot;, Lavabending is a "
                  "specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible "
                  "universe.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]


